{
	"24": {
		"answer_false1": "\u8fdb\u884c\u7a7a\u88ad",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u884c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u4f1a\u589e\u52a0\u822a\u6bcd\u7684\u88ab\u4fa6\u6d4b\u8ba1\u91cf\u6761\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u5904\u4e8e\u8fdb\u6c34\u72b6\u6001",
		"answer_false3": "\u654c\u65b9\u8230\u8239\u89e6\u5e95",
		"answer_false2": "\u5904\u4e8e\u70b9\u71c3\u72b6\u6001",
		"id": 24
	},
	"25": {
		"answer_false1": "\u9ad8\u5371\u6d77\u57df",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u5f00\u542f\u5173\u5361\u7684\u5468\u56de\u6a21\u5f0f\u9700\u8981\u8fbe\u6210\u4e09\u661f\u4ee5\u53ca\uff08\uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u5b89\u5168\u6d77\u57df",
		"answer_false3": "\u4f4e\u5371\u6d77\u57df",
		"answer_false2": "\u5371\u9669\u6d77\u57df",
		"id": 25
	},
	"26": {
		"answer_false1": "70",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u76ee\u524d\u6e38\u620f\u4e2d\u8230\u8239\u7684\u7b49\u7ea7\u4e0a\u9650\u662f\uff08\uff09",
		"answer_right": "120",
		"answer_false3": "100",
		"answer_false2": "90",
		"id": 26
	},
	"27": {
		"answer_false1": "4",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u6bcf\u65e5\u53ef\u4ee5\u5b8c\u6210\u7684\u519b\u4e8b\u59d4\u6258\u6b21\u6570\u662f\uff08\uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u4e0d\u4f5c\u9650\u5236",
		"answer_false3": "15",
		"answer_false2": "8",
		"id": 27
	},
	"28": {
		"answer_false1": "\u7269\u8d44",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u6e38\u620f\u4e2d\u94bb\u77f3\u4e0d\u53ef\u4ee5\u8d2d\u4e70\u7684\u7269\u54c1\u662f\uff08\uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u8230\u8239\u7ecf\u9a8c",
		"answer_false3": "\u5fc3\u667a\u9b54\u65b9",
		"answer_false2": "\u77f3\u6cb9",
		"id": 28
	},
	"15": {
		"answer_false1": "\u987a\u98ce\u822a\u884c",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u4e3a\u4e86\u7f29\u77ed\u98de\u673a\u8d77\u98de\u8ddd\u79bb\uff0c\u822a\u7a7a\u6bcd\u8230\u5728\u8d77\u98de\u98de\u673a\u65f6\u5e94\u8be5\uff08\uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u9006\u98ce\u822a\u884c",
		"answer_false3": "\u9759\u6b62\u4e0d\u52a8",
		"answer_false2": "\u4fa7\u98ce\u822a\u884c",
		"id": 15
	},
	"16": {
		"answer_false1": "\u84b8\u6c7d",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u65b9\u5f0f\u4e0d\u662f\u822a\u6bcd\u6216\u519b\u8230\u5f39\u5c04\u98de\u673a\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u52a8\u529b\u65b9\u5f0f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u673a\u68b0\u5f39\u7c27",
		"answer_false3": "\u6db2\u538b",
		"answer_false2": "\u706b\u836f\u71c3\u6c14",
		"id": 16
	},
	"17": {
		"answer_false1": "\u65d7\u8bed",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u65b9\u5f0f\u4e0d\u662f\u519b\u8230\u4e4b\u95f4\u7684\u901a\u4fe1\u65b9\u5f0f\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u4f20\u58f0\u7ba1",
		"answer_false3": "\u77ed\u6ce2\u65e0\u7ebf\u7535",
		"answer_false2": "\u4fe1\u53f7\u706f",
		"id": 17
	},
	"18": {
		"answer_false1": "\u7403\u9f3b\u578b\u824f",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e2a\u9009\u9879\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e\u8230\u8239\u8230\u824f\u7c7b\u578b\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u88c5\u7532\u578b\u824f",
		"answer_false3": "\u524d\u503e\u578b\u824f",
		"answer_false2": "\u98de\u526a\u578b\u824f",
		"id": 18
	},
	"19": {
		"answer_false1": "\u89e6\u53d1\u5f15\u4fe1",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "VT\u5f15\u4fe1\u53c8\u88ab\u79f0\u4e3a\uff08\uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u65e0\u7ebf\u7535\u8fd1\u70b8\u5f15\u4fe1",
		"answer_false3": "\u6c14\u538b\u5b9a\u9ad8\u5f15\u4fe1",
		"answer_false2": "\u5b9a\u65f6\u5f15\u4fe1",
		"id": 19
	},
	"20": {
		"answer_false1": "\u8fc7\u7a7f\u5f39",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u70ae\u5f39\u672a\u76f4\u63a5\u547d\u4e2d\u8239\u4f53\u800c\u662f\u843d\u5728\u9644\u8fd1\u6d77\u6c34\u4e2d\u7206\u70b8\u7684\u73b0\u8c61\u88ab\u79f0\u4e3a\uff08\uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u8fd1\u5931\u5f39",
		"answer_false3": "\u53cd\u6f5c\u5f39",
		"answer_false2": "\u6c34\u4e2d\u5f39",
		"id": 20
	},
	"21": {
		"answer_false1": "\u4e3b\u70ae",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u9a71\u9010\u8230\u53ef\u4ee5\u901a\u8fc7\uff08\uff09\u6765\u653b\u51fb\u6c34\u4e0b\u7684\u6f5c\u8247",
		"answer_right": "\u6df1\u6c34\u70b8\u5f39",
		"answer_false3": "\u649e\u51fb",
		"answer_false2": "\u9632\u7a7a\u70ae",
		"id": 21
	},
	"22": {
		"answer_false1": "\u901a\u5e38\u5f39",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e2a\u9009\u9879\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e\u6e38\u620f\u4e2d\u8230\u70ae\u7684\u70ae\u5f39\u79cd\u7c7b\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u7167\u660e\u5f39 ",
		"answer_false3": "\u9ad8\u7206\u5f39",
		"answer_false2": "\u7a7f\u7532\u5f39",
		"id": 22
	},
	"23": {
		"answer_false1": "\u6218\u6597\u673a",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u98de\u673a\u4e0d\u4f1a\u8ba1\u5165\u6e38\u620f\u4e2d\u5173\u5361\u7684\u5236\u7a7a\u503c\uff1f",
		"answer_right": "\u53cd\u6f5c\u673a",
		"answer_false3": "\u8f70\u70b8\u673a",
		"answer_false2": "\u9c7c\u96f7\u673a",
		"id": 23
	},
	"all": [
		15,
		16,
		17,
		18,
		19,
		20,
		21,
		22,
		23,
		24,
		25,
		26,
		27,
		28
	]
}